[
    { 
        "question" : "How many KPIs are displayed on the BSC in Insight?", 
        "answers" : [
            { "id" : 0, "text" : "14" },
            { "id" : 1, "text" : "10" },
            { "id" : 2, "text" : "5" },
            { "id" : 3, "text" : "7" }
        ],
        "correct" : 2 
    },
    { 
        "question" : "How many metrics are displayed on the BSC in Insight?", 
        "answers" : [
            { "id" : 0, "text" : "5" },
            { "id" : 1, "text" : "14" },
            { "id" : 2, "text" : "7" },
            { "id" : 3, "text" : "10" }
        ],
        "correct" : 1 
    },
    { 
        "question" : "Where can you find your overall rank and rank of others?", 
        "answers" : [
            { "id" : 0, "text" : "Bottom of each metric" },
            { "id" : 1, "text" : "Fleet Ranking Page" },
            { "id" : 2, "text" : "On the Executive Page" },
            { "id" : 3, "text" : "Cost Center Page" }
        ],
        "correct" : 1 
    },
    { 
        "question" : "Which KPI is weighted the heaviest when calculating your rank?", 
        "answers" : [
            { "id" : 0, "text" : "Profitability" },
            { "id" : 1, "text" : "Zero Defects" },
            { "id" : 2, "text" : "Pure Performance" },
            { "id" : 3, "text" : "Beyond Zero" },
            { "id" : 4, "text" : "People"}
        ],
        "correct" : 3 
    },
    { 
        "question" : "What are the different levels of the BSC?", 
        "answers" : [
            { "id" : 0, "text" : "Executive, Regional, Subregion, Park" },
            { "id" : 1, "text" : "Executive, Regional, Subregion, Cost Center" },
            { "id" : 2, "text" : "Regional, Subregion, Cost Center, Park" },
            { "id" : 3, "text" : "Subregion, Cost Center, Park" }
        ],
        "correct" : 1 
    },
    { 
        "question" : "In the BSC, how do you find more details about each metric?", 
        "answers" : [
            { "id" : 0, "text" : "By hovering over the metric to show the 'i' icon" },
            { "id" : 1, "text" : "By clicking on the BSC metric button" },
            { "id" : 2, "text" : "By clicking on the blue envelope" },
            { "id" : 3, "text" : "By navigating to the home page" }
        ],
        "correct" : 0 
    },
    { 
        "question" : "What happens when you click on a metric in the BSC?", 
        "answers" : [
            { "id" : 0, "text" : "It takes you to the details page" },
            { "id" : 1, "text" : "It shows an information icon" },
            { "id" : 2, "text" : "It updates the data table below" },
            { "id" : 3, "text" : "It takes you to the site page" }
        ],
        "correct" : 2 
    },
    { 
        "question" : "How many metrics in the BSC update on a daily basis?", 
        "answers" : [
            { "id" : 0, "text" : "9" },
            { "id" : 1, "text" : "4" },
            { "id" : 2, "text" : "7" },
            { "id" : 3, "text" : "6" }
        ],
        "correct" : 0 
    },
    { 
        "question" : "How often does the your fleet ranking update?", 
        "answers" : [
            { "id" : 0, "text" : "Daily" },
            { "id" : 1, "text" : "In real time" },
            { "id" : 2, "text" : "Weekly" },
            { "id" : 3, "text" : "Hourly" }
        ],
        "correct" : 0 
    },
    { 
        "question" : "What is the weighted order of KPIs to deterimine fleet ranking?", 
        "answers" : [
            { "id" : 0, "text" : "Beyond Zero, Zero Defects, Profitability, People, Performance" },
            { "id" : 1, "text" : "Zero Defects, Profitability, Performance, People, Beyond Zero" },
            { "id" : 2, "text" : "Performance, Profitability, Beyond Zero, Zero Defects, People" },
            { "id" : 3, "text" : "Beyond Zero, Zero Defects, People, Performance, Profitability" }
        ],
        "correct" : 3 
    },
    { 
        "question" : "What happens to your rank of a KPI if you have NA listed for a metric?", 
        "answers" : [
            { "id" : 0, "text" : "You move slightly higher in rank" },
            { "id" : 1, "text" : "Your rank is not impacted" },
            { "id" : 2, "text" : "you rank is calculated using the other metrics" },
            { "id" : 3, "text" : "You move slightly lower in rank" }
        ],
        "correct" : 2 
    }
]